On vacation, you're free to follow your heart.
People We Meet on Vacation is a romance, comedy,
drama film directed by Brett Haley.
Poppy's a free spirit.
Alex loves a plan.
After years of summer vacations, these polar-opposite pals
wonder if they could be a perfect romantic match.
Poppy Wright, played by Emily Bader.
Alex Nilsen, played by Tom Blyth.
Sarah, played by Sarah Catherine Hook.
Swapna Bakshi-Highsmith, played by Jameela Jamil.
David Nilsen, played by Miles Heizer.
Nam, played by Tommy Do.
People We Meet on Vacation is a 2026 American romantic comedy film directed by Brett Haley from a screenplay
by Yulin Kuang, Amos Vernon, and Nunzio Randazzo, based on the 2021 novel by Emily Henry.
It stars Emily Bader and Tom Blyth.
Polar opposites, Poppy wants to explore the world while Alex would prefer to stay home with a good book, but
surprisingly they become best friends after sharing a car to their small Ohio hometown from Boston.
They live far apart, but for a decade they have shared one week of summer
vacation together, which finally leads to a deeper connection.
The film was released on Netflix on January 9, 2026.
It received generally positive reception.
The film explores themes of friendship, based on novel
or book, romcom, grief, summer vacation.
The tone is lighthearted and emotional.